

TRAN HUYNH HUY HAO

Frontend Developer

Dob: 29/06/1999

Gender: Male

Phone: 0775713079

Email: tranhuynhhuyhao@gmail.com

Website: linkedin.com/in/hao-tran-huynh-huy-7452a524b/

Address: 203/1A Luu Huu Phuoc str, 15 ward, district 8. Ho Chi Minh City.

OBJECTIVE

I have experience worked in Frontend Developer with knowledge of React and Vue. I used to participate in 2 projects using Vue framework combined with many libraries and design UI/UX by figma. My plan is becoming a fullstack engineer so i'll start learning BE stuffs after i'm proficient in FE.

EDUCATION

2017 - 2021

NGUYEN TAT THANH UNIVERSITY

Software Engineer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

07/2022 - 03/2023

Interloan Vietnam

Frontend Developer

Main responsibilities:

Experienced software developer with expertise in Fintech. Proficient in using Vuejs for maintenance and improvement of Interloan system.

Achievement and awards:

- Maintained and improved the Interloan system using Vuejs.
- Designed user-friendly and visually appealing UI/UX interfaces with Figma.
- Implemented authentication with Axios for secure user access.
- · Managed role and permission for users using Casl.
- Deployed the system using a bundle-based web server with Vite.
- · Maintained consistent system state using Vuex and Pinia.
- Utilized templates from Vuetify and Vuexy to create an attractive and functional system.

06/2020 - 09/2020

FPT Software

Java Internship.

Main responsibilities:

- Researching and learning Java language and Spring framework.
- Additionally, learning HTML, CSS and Javascript to contribute the team that work on a selling bus tikets website.

Achievement and awards:

- Learned about java, spring-mvc, tomcat apache, mysql, spring-boot, spring-hibernate.
- Support team to perform the main function of the website.
- Support team to edit the website interface and database.

SKILLS

Designer tools	Figma
Programming Language	JavaScript, TypeScript.
Framework	ReactJs, VueJs.
Others	Vuex, Pinia, Vuetify, MaterialUI, Redux, Git, Github, Gitlab.

PROJECTS

EWA - Earned Wage Access (https://luong.interloan.tech)

(09/2022 - present)

Project status	Go live
Description project	The platform would likely involve employees submitting a request for a salary advance, and then the application would verify their employment and earnings to determine the amount of the advance that can be provided. The advance would then be disbursed to the employee, either through direct deposit or another method. The employee would repay the advance through deductions from their future paychecks. This concept aims to provide financial support to employees in need and help them manage their cash flow.
Team size	5 (3 backend, 2 frontend).
Position in project	Frontend developer
Responsibility in project	 Collect and understand the needs and requirements of the customer to ensure that the final product meets their expectations. Analyze the customer requirements to ensure that they are feasible and make sense. Use Figma to create user-friendly and visually appealing interfaces for the web application. Use TypeScript, Vue.js framework, Tailwind, and Git to build the web application according to the design and customer requirements.
Technology description	Figma, Typescript, Vuejs, Pinia, Tailwind, SCSS, axios, i18n, Vue-Router, Gitlab.

ILUONG - (app.iluong.vn)

(12/2022 - present)

Project status	Go live
Description project	iLuong is a web application that enables users to calculate and manage their salaries conveniently and accurately. The app features advanced salary, tax, and benefits
	calculation tools, as well as the ability to create personal profiles and store relevant

	information. With iLuong, individuals and businesses can efficiently manage their salary-related matters with ease.
Team size	5 (3 backend, 2 frontend).
Position in project	Frontend developer
Responsibility in project	 Collect customer needs and requirements to ensure that the final product meets their expectations. Design UI/UX for application. Calculate salaries by leveraging my understanding of money flow. Handle upload and export file. Use Javascript, Vue.js framework, Vue-bootstrap, and Git to build the web application according to the design and customer requirements.
Technology description	Figma, Javascript, Vuejs, Pinia, Vue-bootstrap, axios, i18n, Vue-Router, Gitlab.

© topcv.vn